waresphere.com 2017-06-16

# Privacy Policy

## **Overview**

This privacy policy sets out how WareSphere Online Store uses and protects any information that you give WareSphere Online Store when you use this website. WareSphere Online Store is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. WareSphere Online Store may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

By accepting the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, you expressly consent to us collecting, using and disclosing your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.

## Collection of Personal Information

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section. 

To open your WareSphere Account, we need to obtain certain personal information from you, such as your full name, address, email, phone number and your fax number. You will be required to provide information to our third party payment provider to authorize your payment. For certain high value transactions, we may be required to report personal information to the relevant authorities or partners.

However, we do not collect any financial information such as credit or debit card details. For verification purposes we reserve the right to request proof of your identity and proof of address. When using our services, your IP address and login times are recorded and stored for purposes of preventing fraud and enhancing the security of our services. We may also collect usage and access data that allows us to prevent multiple account openings or other fraudulent behavior or to protect our systems against illegal attacks or abuse. Strictly for this purpose, we may share such data with specialized and trustworthy fraud management services that help us analyse the data. We may also use cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. Information collected and stored through cookies may be matched against the personal data we hold on our systems. 

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests. 

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes 
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at admin@waresphere.com 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Suite 4, 1289 Zizhu Road, Kunshan 215300 China. 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

## Links

This website contains links to third party websites. Please be aware that WareSphere is not responsible for the privacy practices of these third party websites. We encourage users to read the privacy statements of each website they visit by clicking a link on our website. This privacy statement applies solely to the WareSphere website and the WareSphere services.

## Security

WareSphere protects your personal data against unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Once logged into your Account, all internet communication is secured using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology with high security 128bit encryption, certified by Comodo CA Limited. And all payment transactions will be secured as well. You must never share your Account or login details with anyone. If you are concerned that any of your login details have been compromised, you can change them any time you like once you are logged on, however you should immediately contact Customer Services and tell us why you think your login details have been compromised.

## Notification of Changes

Changes to this privacy statement are posted on our website. If we are going to use your personal data in a manner different to the uses stated at the time of collection we will also notify you via email. You may object to any new use of your personal data by contacting Customer Service, however, we will treat such an objection as a notice to terminate your WareSphere Account.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

## List of cookies we collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE name | COOKIE Description  
---|---  
CART | The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO | Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
COMPARE | The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CURRENCY | Your preferred currency  
CUSTOMER | An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH | An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS | Stores the Customer Segment ID  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE | A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
FRONTEND | You sesssion ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY | The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT | The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE | Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE | Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL | The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
POLLN | Information on what polls you have voted on.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED | The items that you have recently compared.   
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST | An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT | The number of items in your Wishlist.
